Dead Bodies is a drama, thriller film directed by Robert Quinn.
The return of a vengeful ex-girlfriend sets into motion a series of gruesome events for
a hapless Irish bachelor in director Robert Quinn's grim black comedy.
Tommy (Andrew Scott) had thought he had seen the last of Jean (Katy Davis) after their recent breakup, but when she returns to stake
her claim on Tommy's apartment, the confrontation that ensues makes their previous quarrels look petty by comparison.
After leaving the apartment in the head of the fight to cool his head and gather his thoughts, he returns only to find that Jean has died and
enlists the aid of his friend Noel (Darren Healy) in ditching the body and ensuring that no one ever finds out what happened.
Tommy McGann, played by Andrew Scott.
Jean Goodman, played by Katy Davis.
Viv McCormack, played by Kelly Reilly.
Noel, played by Darren Healy.
Billy, played by Eamonn Owens.
Mr. O'Leary, played by Jer O'Leary.
Dead Bodies is a 2003 Irish comedy thriller film by Robert Quinn starring Andrew
Scott, Katy Davis, Eamonn Owens, Darren Healy and Kelly Reilly.
The screenplay was written by Derek Landy.
It was the first film shot in Ireland on high definition.
It was filmed in four and a half weeks in Dublin.
The film premiered in cinemas on 25 April 2003 and was
released on DVD on 24 October 2003.
The tone is emotional and intense.